<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>
        <title>Recent Service disruptions News</title>
        <link>https://news.uoit.ca</link>
        <description>Recent Service disruptions</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:33:18 EDT</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:33:18 EDT</lastBuildDate>
        <ttl>5</ttl>
        <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/uoitnews" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <feedburner:info xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" uri="http://news.uoit.ca/index.xml"/>
        <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/>        
                                                                                <item>
            <title>Overnight repairs to Science Building East Atrium elevator October 12 to 13</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <div><a href="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/overnight-repairs-to-science-building-east-atrium-elevator-october-12-to-13.php" title="Overnight repairs to Science Building East Atrium elevator October 12 to 13"><img src="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/images/Thumbnail-ScienceBuilding.jpg" alt="Science Building at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology&apos;s north Oshawa location." width="100" /></a></div>
                    <div>The elevator in the Science Building, East Atrium (next to Tim Hortons) will be out of service from Thursday, October 12 at 5 p.m. to Friday, October 13 at 7 a.m. to allow for repairs. </div>
                ]]>
            </description>                    
            <link>https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/overnight-repairs-to-science-building-east-atrium-elevator-october-12-to-13.php</link>
            <guid>https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/overnight-repairs-to-science-building-east-atrium-elevator-october-12-to-13.php</guid>
            <summary>The elevator in the Science Building, East Atrium (next to Tim Hortons) will be out of service from Thursday, October 12 at 5 p.m. to Friday, October 13 at 7 a.m. to allow for repairs. </summary>                
                            <category>service disruption</category>
                                                                                                                                                            <media:content description="Science Building at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology's north Oshawa location." url="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/images/Thumbnail-ScienceBuilding.jpg">
                <media:description>Science Building at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology's north Oshawa location.</media:description>
            </media:content>
                        <article><![CDATA[<p>The elevator in the Science Building, East Atrium (next to Tim Hortons) will be out of service from Thursday, October 12 at 5 p.m. to Friday, October 13 at 7 a.m. to allow for repairs.</p>
<p>Please use the other elevator near the west entrance of the building between these hours.</p>
<p>For more information, contact <a href="mailto:Ken.Bright@uoit.ca" title="email Ken Bright">Ken Bright</a>, Director, Office of Campus Infrastructure and Sustainability, at ext. 2532.</p>]]></article>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:28:00 EDT</pubDate>
        </item>
                                                                                                                <item>
            <title>Secure-and-hold drill at north and downtown Oshawa locations – October 31 and November 1</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <div><a href="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/secure-and-hold-drill-at-north-and-downtown-oshawa-locations--october-31-and-november-1.php" title="Secure-and-hold drill at north and downtown Oshawa locations – October 31 and November 1"><img src="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/images/Thumbnail_Secure_And_Hold.jpg" alt="Secure-and-hold shield" width="100" /></a></div>
                    <div>The University of Ontario Institute of Technology and Durham College are committed to maintaining a safe campus environment. As part of this commitment, the Office of Campus Safety will conduct a series of secure-and-hold drills.</div>
                ]]>
            </description>                    
            <link>https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/secure-and-hold-drill-at-north-and-downtown-oshawa-locations--october-31-and-november-1.php</link>
            <guid>https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/secure-and-hold-drill-at-north-and-downtown-oshawa-locations--october-31-and-november-1.php</guid>
            <summary>The University of Ontario Institute of Technology and Durham College are committed to maintaining a safe campus environment. As part of this commitment, the Office of Campus Safety will conduct a series of secure-and-hold drills.</summary>                
                            <category>service disruption</category>
                            <category>students</category>
                                                                                                                                                            <media:content description="Secure-and-hold shield" url="https://news.uoit.ca/archives/2017/10/images/Thumbnail_Secure_And_Hold.jpg">
                <media:description>Secure-and-hold shield</media:description>
            </media:content>
                        <article><![CDATA[<p>The University of Ontario Institute of Technology and Durham College are committed to maintaining a safe campus environment. As part of this commitment, the Office of Campus Safety will conduct a series of secure-and-hold drills.</p>
<p>The drills will be held on:</p>
<ul type="disc">
<li>Tuesday, October 31 at 9:45 a.m.: the university&#8217;s and college&#8217;s shared campus location, including Campus Corners.</li>
<li>Wednesday, November 1 at 9:45 a.m.: the university&#8217;s downtown campus location.</li>
</ul>
<p>A secure-and-hold is used to ensure public safety when a lockdown is <b>not</b> required but public safety is an issue. During a secure-and-hold drill or event, everyone has full access into and throughout campus buildings, but people should not to go outside the building, and should stay away from external windows and doors.</p>
<p><b>Secure-and-hold drill description:</b></p>
<ul>
<li>A campuswide voice mail message will be sent to faculty and staff office phones as a reminder of the drill prior to 9:45 a.m.</li>
<li>A drill advisory message will be broadcast on the campus public address (PA) system, starting at 8:50 a.m. This message will be repeated several times prior to the start of the drill.</li>
<li>Upon hearing the announcement of the commencement of the drill, students, faculty and staff will follow the procedures listed below. These procedures can also be found on the <a href="http://shared.uoit.ca/shared/department/campus-safety/documents/secure-and-hold.pdf" target="_blank" title="Secure and Hold procedures">Office of Campus Safety website</a>, the Emergency Guideline posters found on campus, and the flyers distributed the morning of the drill.
<ul>
<li>Once the drill is complete, the all-clear will be given over the PA system and the campus will return to normal activities.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p><b>Secure-and-hold procedures</b></p>
<p>The secure-and-hold announcement will be made over the PA system.</p>
<p><b>Once the secure-and-hold is announced, follow these instructions:</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Follow the directions given to you by Campus Security.</li>
<li>Do not exit the building unless directed to do so.</li>
<li>Stay away from exterior doors and windows.</li>
<li>If you are outside and you receive a secure-and-hold warning message, go to the nearest building.</li>
<li>If it is safe to do so, you may return to normal activities during a secure-and-hold.</li>
</ul>
<p><b>If the fire alarm sounds during the secure-and-hold:</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Assess your area for signs of fire.</li>
<li>If no sign of fire, wait for further instructions.</li>
<li>If signs of fire, evacuate if safe to do so.</li>
<li>If you choose to evacuate, use the safest exit.</li>
</ul>
<p>The university and college realize an exercise of this nature can be an unwanted distraction; however, it is necessary to maintain the highest level of safety and security for students, faculty, staff and visitors. We also understand this experience may be unsettling for some individuals. Faculty and staff can access counselling services through the <a href="https://www.uoit.ca/current-students/campus-services/health-centre/campus-health-centre/index.php" title="Campus Health Centre">Campus Health Centre</a> after the drills.</p>
<p>The campus will remain open during the drills and traffic is permitted to enter or leave the premises normally.</p>
<p>The Office of Campus Safety will also use the Campus Incident Response Emergency Notification System (CIRENS) to notify students, faculty and staff during the secure-and-hold drills. Students are encouraged to follow their school on Twitter to receive CIRENS messages, not only for this exercise, but for all emergent situations on campus.&#160; In addition, students can provide feedback on the drill itself via the <a href="http://www.uoit.ca/lockdownfeedback" title="lockdown feedback form">feedback form</a> located on the Office of Campus Safety website.</p>]]></article>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
        </item>
        </channel>
</rss>